I know look reading through pre-draft
projections of where you're going to
play. A lot of people say you can you
can go tackle, you can play guard. Where
is it that you feel most comfortable
playing?
>> I feel comfortable playing anywhere. You
know, whatever I can do to put my team
in the best light to go win games, I'm
going to do whatever coach tells me to
do and, you know, go out there and
provide for the team in any way I can.
>> Appreciate it, man. Thanks again. Nice
to meet you. And like I said,
congratulations.
>> Nice to meet you, too. Thank you,
>> Chris.
Hey Kayen, uh Chris Perkins from the
South Florida some Sentinel.
Congratulations on your first round pick
here. Um let me ask you, are you
surprised that you went to Miami? How
much contact did you have with the
Dolphins? And where were you generally
thinking that you would be drafted?
>> I I thought I was, you know, top 15, top
20. That's kind of where my range was,
you know, just, you know, to talk to my
agents. You know, I thought that the
draft was going to start at 12 for me
and that's that's exactly what happened.
Um, but man, this is just a crazy
surreal feeling.
But, you know, had some good talks at
the 30 visit with the Dolphins. I mean,
we kind of hit it off right away and,
you know, I love the coaching staff down
there. You know, I'm very excited to get
down there.
Right.
>> Thank you. Congratulations.
>> Thank you.
David.
>> Hey Kaden, congratulations. David
Feronis of the South Florida Sun
Sentenno here. How you doing, sir?
>> I'm I'm good. How are you doing?
>> Abs. I bet you're doing good.
No, I know you're a massive human being
who has a lot of power in his game. What
is your mindset when you get downhill
and have a defender in front of you,
>> man? I mean, that's O line play, bro.
It's it's physical. It's physicality.
You trying to you trying to put the man
on the ground, man. Move it. move a man
against his will. Like that's that's my
favorite part about the game. And I know
that, you know, we're we're we're going
to run out the ball, man. We we we going
to do that thing, man. I can't wait to
go in there and build relationships with
my teammates and and just have fun and
just just sit down and learn and just be
be a student of the game.
>> Right. Thanks.
>> Thank you,
>> Isaiah.
>> Hey, what's going on, Kayen? Welcome to
Miami, man. How you feeling? Feeling I'm
feeling blessed, man. Overly blessed,
man. It's such a blessing for real.
>> That's what's up. You talked about
runningit out of the ball. Um, how is it
going to feel blocking for first time
pro bowler Devon Han?
>> Going to feel so good, man. Knowing that
he you blocking for a guy that makes
your job easier, man. You just sustain
your block for as long as you can and
and you know, give effort and have that
grit and toughness, man. We He's going
to make plays, man. He's a He's a great
running back, man. Fast as hell, man. I
can't wait to block for him.
>> Cool. Appreciate you, man.
>> Sir,
>> how
>> hi Kaden, can you hear me now?
>> Yes sir, I can hear you.
>> Hi. Congratulations, Hal with the Palm
Beach Post. Um, you had mentioned your
30 visit with the Dolphins. What were
your impressions of coach Halfley and
uh, general manager John Eric Sullivan?
>> Man, I love I love the meetings with
them. I mean, they they laid it out for
me, you know, kind of kind of just laid
it down and told me how it was. You
know, they're they're straight shooters
and I love that, you know, in a coach
and a GM. Um, and and they told me like
we're we're we're trying to play fast,
physical, tough football and I told them
I'm I'm ready to go. you know, day one
and and be with my team. And I feel like
that's what exactly what we can do to
get that culture started over there.
>> One other thing before I let you run on
to the next one real quick. Um, we've
seen clips of you with the ball in your
hands. Tell us about your skills with
the ball in your hands.
>> Yeah, it's really just about, you know,
the trust factor. I I go out there and I
just try to handle my business. Like I
said, I play guard, I play tackle, I
play center. Doesn't matter, you know,
wide receiver. If if that means that I'm
going out there to help my team win in
any way, I'mma do it. Like, no question.
>> All right. Thank you. Good luck,
>> sir. Thank you.
>> Mike Kuno,
>> Kayen, congrats. Welcome to South
Florida. Mike Kuno, CBS News Miami. Um,
you you mentioned, you know, meeting
Sullivan and Halfley on on your visit
here. Can you walk us through the phone
call you had when they called to let you
know? Do you even remember it at the at
this point? I know things are probably
spinning. Man, I tal I talked to a lot
of a lot of guys on the phone. They were
kind of passing the phone around, but I
was I was just so locked into, you know,
God blessed me with this opportunity,
man. Tears flowing down the face. It's
it's still surreal, but like I said, I'm
I'm ready to get down there and and I
know Coach Hley and we're we're we're
going to build a great bond and I'm
gonna have fun down there.
>> David
Hey Kayen, David Ferronis again. How do
you feel about the athleticism in your
game outside zone blocks and such? Uh
what do you think of your game in in in
that regard?
>> I feel great about it. You know, as as I
keep the, you know, the weight in check,
you know, under 55, under 50. I believe
that I can play all, you know, all 60
minutes, you know, as fast as I can. Um
and and really just be, you know, that
fast, physical, explosive guy that I
know that I am. and you know just kind
of using my skills you know to my
advantage going out there and playing
fast and free.
>> Excellent. Appreciate it.
>> Yes, sir.
>> Mark.
>> Hey uh Kayen. I'm Mark Sto with the
Miami Times. Welcome to Miami. Thank
you.
>> Uh just had a quick question. What
sacrifices or challenges from your past
do you think will f fuel you the most at
this level? Yeah, I mean I, you know,
had some, you know, family stuff going
on. You know, different things like, you
know, my parents ain't the ain't the
richest. So, I feel like that that's
definitely an external motivator. Like,
I'm playing for the name on my back. I'm
playing for my family. Um, and and I'm
playing for the guys, you know, around
me, you know, for the relationship that
I built with those guys. Um, but I'm
blessed for the opportunity. You know,
God has placed me in a in a great place
and I'm ready to go.
Hassan.
>> Hey Kaden, congratulations on getting
drafted to the Miami Dolphins. Uh my
name is Hassan Battel and I'm with the
By Reason Sports Network. First of all,
congratulations. How you feeling
tonight,
>> sir? Thank you so much. I appreciate
you. You know, you talked about Jeff
Hafley and John Eric Sullivan being
straight shooters. And you know, uh,
your former Alabama head coach, Nick
Sabin, is also a straight straight sho
shooter, and he said it publicly, and
I'm quoting him directly, uh, when he's
not in the building, you know, meaning
you, he might not be in the best shape.
He's not a selfarter. How do you respond
to that? And what does your preparation
look like now, now that you're in the
NFL and you're playing with the Miami
Dolphins? Yeah, I mean, yeah, it it
definitely was. It was like that. You
know, I was 400 lb, you know, when and
Coach S was there, you know, in the
offseason. Um, you know, that summer, my
freshman year, but I feel like I've, you
know, got a couple years under my belt
to where I've I've kept that in check,
you know, I've built and and put a plan
in place to to go succeed and to to be
at the weight that I need to be um to go
out there and provide for the team. So,
Michelle
Hi, thanks and congratulations. Welcome
to Miami. I'm just wondering uh I'm from
the Miami Herald. What do you know about
Miami and about the idea of living in
Miami, the Miami lifestyle? Do you ever
come here on vacation? What do you know
about Miami? Thanks.
>> I haven't been to Florida too too much.
You know, I I've been down to Dest
with my boys on spring break. But, um,
the first time I was at Miami, well,
Fort Lauderdale was for my 30 visit.
And, you know, I love the city. Um, and
I feel like it's it's going to be a good
time. You know, have have a fun time
down there. Um, but the biggest thing
for me is, hey, man, no state taxes.
That's a blessing right there. A
blessing.